Join channel t.me/dongworld agar tidak ketinggalan update.
Sub indo akan rilis dalam beberapa menit kedepan.
A huge explosion of three thousand flames is about to devour the entire star field
critical moment
The three giants of Danta had no choice but to close the star field
Xiao Yan is left alone in the Star Territory
Fight against the three thousand flames with unyielding will
experienced a protracted life-and-death struggle
Xiao Yan finally seized the opportunity to completely control Sanqian Yanhuo.
Just when the Dan Pagoda was about to withstand the disaster of blazing fire in the star field,
Xiao Yan breaks through the tower and comes out
Everyone, get out of here quickly
alright
Stop making trouble
Disperse quickly
It's Xiao Yan
three presidents
Stay safe
It's Xiao Yan
Oh my God
He actually came out alive from the star field explosion
Xiao Yan
I said he must be fine
My dragon seal will never go wrong
The little girl talks duplicity
You are no less worried than the Little Doctor Fairy
You're talking nonsense. Shut up.
Feel sorry
Made you worry
Xiao Yan
What are you
Collected the Three Thousand Yan Yanhuo
Uncle Xuan doesn’t want to take it back, right?
You have helped Danta solve a big problem.
But luckily you're fine
Otherwise
Get rid of drug dust in the future
They will definitely come to us and cause trouble.
During your time in Star Territory
we also got some
Information about Yao Chen’s imprisonment
According to the information we got
The Soul Palace has transferred Yaochen out of Hades City.
Where is that teacher being detained now?
There are clues
But not sure yet
It takes time to verify
But don't worry
Medicine dust is of great use to the Soul Palace
They will not harm his life unless absolutely necessary
You just need to wait for the news with peace of mind
teacher
Don't worry
Disciples will come to rescue you soon
The pain that the Soul Palace has given you
I will definitely pay it back a thousand times
Young Master Yi Chen
You are finally here
Sect Leader Chen invited me to come
But because of Chen Xian’s death in the alchemy world
Exactly
The dog died in the Dan world
That's what Soul Palace Mu Gu did.
I hope Tianming Sect can make the decision for me
Sect Master Chen, could it be that he has forgotten
Our Tianming Sect has already formed an alliance with the Soul Palace
It stands to reason that Xuanming Sect is affiliated with Tianming Sect.
Our sect should make the decision for you
But for the personal affairs of Sect Leader Chen
Hurt the harmony between the sect and its allies
I'm afraid it's inappropriate
That
Children's hatred
Before I heard that Chen Xian met Old Man Mu Gu
He was severely injured by a guy named Xiao Yan
Otherwise, with Chen Xian’s strength
He may not be implicated by the old man Mu Gu
Is this possible?
It's true
That's it
Xiao Yan is the culprit
Without him, he would have provoked the Soul Palace to injure Chen Xian.
Then there won’t be so much trouble
yes
So be it
This young master and you went to take Xiao Yan’s head.
Sect Leader Wei Chen let out such a bad breath
As for old man Mu Gu,
I will be a peacemaker again
Introduce you to the Soul Palace
Later, he tried to compensate Master Chen
What do you think?
cut
Follow the arrangements of Young Master Yi Chen
Kaishan Seal
Cover the ground
print
Your cultivation speed is really terrifying
strange fire
Emperor Seal Jue
And the terrifying fire lotus
If you use all your strength
I'm afraid that ordinary Dou Zun is no match for you.
Senior Tianhuo was so complimentary
But it's not just you
Even the little medical fairy may have reached the peak of the three-star fighting master.
This speed of cultivation is really enviable
In just one year, Senior Tianhuo
Just stabilize your strength at the peak of One Star Dou Zun
I think
You break through two stars
Even regain the previous strength
It's just a matter of time
How can it be so easy
want to restore
I'm afraid it will take some time.
Normal practice does take a lot of time
But Senior Tianhuo may have forgotten
I am an eighth-grade alchemist
This is
This elixir is Poria Green Pill
Able to quickly restore strength to those whose strength has deteriorated
After Senior Tianhuo took it
It is not a problem to quickly restore to Samsung Dou Zun in a short time.
boy
you
Along the way
Senior Tianhuo helped this junior a lot
Juniors are not ungrateful people
I will remember it
Where's mine?
I also want the eighth-grade elixir
All flavors are wanted
I want to eat
OK OK
can't forget you
Right
Why didn’t you see Elder Ye Zhong and Xin Lan?
Not long ago, Elder Ye Zhong took Xinlan back to Ye's house to handle housework.
Before leaving
let me give you a letter
It was said to be from the Gama Empire.
Third brother
Farewell till now
I don’t know how you are doing in Zhongzhou
since you left
The Flame Alliance is under the management of Queen Medusa
It’s no longer what it used to be
Already the overlord of the northwest corner of Dou Qi Continent
All forces came here to form an alliance.
And Hai Lao also successfully promoted to Douzong
It is also a great help from Yanmeng
It’s just that Queen Medusa has been a little strange lately
But don't worry
I’ve asked the snake tribe’s high priest to take a look at it.
What's going on
this
I have to ask Xiao Yan to make more elixirs for me.
Xiao Yan
little medical fairy
Could you please help me deliver these two letters to Elder Ye Zhong?
Let him be sent back to the Jiama Empire
Don't worry
Xiao Yan, little friend
Chen Tiannan, the leader of Xuanming Sect
Leading a group of subordinates to name and cause trouble for you.
Xiao Yan, get out of here quickly
Today you must give justice to my Xuanming Sect
What's going on
Why did our Danta champion provoke their Xuanming Sect?
I heard that it was Xiao Yan who beat his son seriously.
As a result, his son died again at the hands of others
Isn’t this person gone? Then he comes to trouble Xiao Yan.
What the hell logic?
Chen Tiannan
You are also the leader of a sect
Now I'm making a lot of noise in my Danta like a shrew
In what manner
Elder Qiu
Hand over Xiao Yan quickly
Let this be settled
Otherwise I will never give up
bully the weak and fear the strong
What do you think Danta is?
Let's do it as you say
Danta
So majestic
Who is this guy?
Your Xuanming Sect doesn’t even have this rule?
What kind of shrimps, soldiers and crabs dare to interrupt casually?
Under the Tianming Sect
Yi Chen
Yi Yichen
Yi Xiuluo Yi Chen, who is known as the next sect leader
Legend has it that he is in a forbidden area
A ruthless man who devoured his brothers' fighting spirit and flesh and blood together.
Elder Qiu
This matter is Uncle Chen’s family matter
Revenge for murder
I'm afraid it would be inappropriate for Danta to interfere.
You Tianming Sect can intervene in this matter
The Xuanming Sect and my Tianming Sect share the same spirit.
I can't ignore it
If we don’t hand over Xiao Yan, our Tianming Sect will give up our neutrality.
Join forces with Soul Palace
you
But I heard that Xiao Yan became the new champion of Danta
It's indeed rude to ask for someone by force.
I don’t want to get into a fight and involve others.
Why don't you call out your new champion?
I had a private discussion with him
Settle this account
how
Ah what
Everyone knows Yi Shura's viciousness
No matter how strong Xiao Yan is, he may not be his opponent.
But Xiao Yan would be ruined if he didn't fight for the title of Danta Champion.
So despicable
Elder Qiu
I'm not asking too much, right?
Just a little discussion
Is it possible that this Danta champion is made of paper?
Afraid of breaking it
Your Excellency used the reputation of Danta to force me.
If I retreat
Wouldn’t that make people laugh?
I accepted your challenge.
Xiao Yan
If you hadn't beaten my son seriously,
My son will not die at the hands of Mu Gu
you
Okay, okay, got it
It's my fault that your son died.
Let's go
This is not a place for fighting
follow me
Danhui champion Xiao Yan wants to compete with Tianming Sect Shura Yichen
This kind of thing is rare in Danta.
After all, alchemists are gentle people
Come on Xiao Yan
Come on, Xiao Yan
The flesh and blood of Danhui champion
I'm very interested
Fight if you want
Stop talking nonsense
If you want to die early, I will satisfy you
good
But that's all
bloody explosion
Obediently donate your flesh and blood
What a powerful alien fire
It’s the first time I’ve seen an alchemist so good at fighting.
Well done Xiao Yan
beat him hard
This guy is weird
Looks like I need to show some real skills.
seven kill gun
This is the end for Xiao Yan
Cool
Well done
It's better to be famous than to meet
This Yi Chen is not good at it.
Xiao Yan is obviously too strong
Who would have thought that an alchemist could have such strong combat power?
you pissed me off
Xiao Yan
I don't believe I can't deal with you today
Tian Ming Shura Hand
Something interesting this time
Kaishan Seal
Turn over the sea seal
Covering the ground
Our Danta champion actually defeated Yi Shuluo
It turns out that alchemists can be so good at fighting.
This doesn't seem to affect Sven at all.
Xiao Yan be careful
Boy, pay for my son's life
Attack the alchemist in the realm of Dan Pagoda
You Xuanming Sect and Tianming Sect want to be the enemy of my Danta.
I can't do anything to you today
The hatred of killing a son is irreconcilable
Xiao Yan
You'd better stay in Danta for the rest of your life
Walk
Xiao Yan, my Tianming Sect will not let you go.
Meet Senior Xuan Yi
Just don't pay attention to this kind of thing from now on
Our Danta will keep you safe
How can we back down when they knock on the door?
You
This temperament is exactly the same as that guy's
As expected of master and disciple
alright
come with us
We found his whereabouts