Join channel t.me/dongworld to stay updated.
Donghua is translated by DongWorld.
Preview Previous episode:
Xiao Yan tries to help his teacher, Yao Lao, recover his soul power.
He brought his companions to the Bone Mountains.
Searching for the whereabouts of the Spirit Fruit.
Inside the Bone Mountains,
The Wind and Thunder Pavilion attacked the disciples of the Falling Star Pavilion.
In a critical situation,
Xiao Yan arrived just in time.
Killing the invading enemy.
After understanding the situation,
Xiao Yan led his companions to suppress the Wind and Thunder Pavilion.
They recaptured the Falling Star Pavilion headquarters.
While everyone was waiting for the opening of the ancient relic,
Zi Yan was suddenly attacked by a mysterious person.
Although Xiao Yan acted immediately,
the perpetrator managed to escape.
The seal is about to be opened.
The ancient relic is about to be opened.
Elder Hu, this journey is extremely dangerous.
The more people will be targeted.
The few of us should just leave.
You arrange the others to stay here,
Be ready for assistance.
Okay, Young Leader.
Let's go.
Teacher.
Unexpectedly, Elder Huang Xuan also came.
The Wind and Thunder Pavilion also joined in the excitement.
It seems that this ancient relic is very interesting.
With Elder Huang Xuan present,
The Wind and Thunder Pavilion will probably return empty-handed.
Xiao Yan.
Tian Yao Huang Clan,
Ice Valley,
Wind and Thunder Pavilion,
Xuanming Sect.
Truly an unexpected encounter.
Xiao Yan.
Long time no see.
I never thought you could reach the Dou Zun level.
Hmph.
As if the Tian Yao Huang Clan is so great.
In my eyes,
You are just a bunch of rotten birds.
Who are you?
Dare to speak so casually!
Stupid little kid.
Don't worry.
After this,
Qing'er will also receive the clan's inheritance.
Reaching the Dou Zun level is not difficult.
You are the Xiao Yan who holds the blood of our clan, yes?
If you had remained in the Central Plains,
perhaps we couldn't have done anything.
But now you've come alone.
With just the strength of a two star Dou Zun?
Has your mouth always been this loud?
With the Tian Yao Huang Clan handling Xiao Yan,
I don't need to bother.
Without the protection of the Pill Pagoda,
I want to see,
how you can turn things around.
This ancient relic is really bustling.
Xiao Yan, you really came.
Miss Huo'er.
Brother Xiao Yan.
Long time no see.
I hope you are well.
Xiao Yan pays his respects to Valley Leader.
In just two years,
Brother Xiao Yan has not only won the Pill Conference,
but has also reached the Dou Zun level.
This speed,
really amazes me.
He is the champion of the Pill Conference, Xiao Yan.
I didn't expect it.
His talent is truly extraordinary.
Just luck.
Your words are really annoying.
I didn't expect you to come too.
It seems that this ancient relic is really special.
Dou Sheng inheritance is extremely rare.
Moreover, there are rumors of a sky-level combat technique.
I must definitely bring Huo'er to take a look.
Everyone,
Brother Xiao Yan has done me a favor.
If anyone dares to hurt him,
The Blazing Fire Valley will fight back,
although it might not be as strong as them.
If the Blazing Flame Valley supports Xiao Yan,
it will be difficult to capture him in a short period of time.
Moreover, our target is not him.
You are lucky today.
Once our business is done, then we will deal with you.
Thank you, Leader Tang.
The seal is about to break.
Come on, first come first served!
A terrifying spatial seal.
After so many years,
still has such a powerful strength.
Truly a Dou Sheng relic.
Each puppet has the strength of a peak Dou Zong.
This is probably a test from senior Dou Sheng.
Below the Dou Zong level,
have no right to enter the relic and receive its inheritance.
Ordinary puppets, just destroy them.
With just a few Dou Zong level puppets,
hope to stop me?
Can evolve through formations.
Puppet Master,
After evolving, it is at least equivalent to a two star Dou Zun.
Xuang Sect Elder is probably going to be unlucky.
Just a bluff.
Why did this puppet's strength suddenly soar?
If I can subdue them all,
plus my demon puppet,
even against a five star Dou Zun,
I have a chance.
Senior, let me help you.
Please hold on for a few minutes.
Young man, hurry up.
I can't hold on for long.
Does he want to subdue these puppets?
Relax, Qing'er.
What we can't get, he can't get either.
He also has a puppet like this.
No wonder he acted.
Leader Tang.
I'll go first.
Brother Xiao Yan.
We will meet again soon.
Let's go.
We're going in too.
Xiao Yan.
Everyone be careful.
Follow me.
It's been a long time,
Why did you come back here?
This fire path is probably sealed.
If it continues like this,
it will be hard to find a way out.
Often the most dangerous place,
is actually the safest.
That's right.
The fire path is a trap.
The magma below is the way out.
Come on.
Truly a test from Dou Sheng.
Who would have thought that the way out was under the magma.
This must be the original relic.
Let them fight over the sky-level combat technique.
Our main target is the Spirit Fruit.
Zi Yan, it's up to you now.
Relax, leave it to me.
The aroma of medicine is strongest here.
It must be here.
Let's go in.
This place is much better than Wanyao Mountains.
Come on, find the Soul Fruit.
Here it is.
This is the Soul Tree.
Zi Yan, you're great.
Then what are you waiting for?
Let's attack.
Listen to the boss's orders.
Heavenly and earthly objects must be guarded by strange creatures.
This Spirit Fruit is a treasure to fill the soul.
This place can't possibly be peaceful.
Zi Yan is right.
Everyone be careful.
So it's a Heavenly Dragon.
This ancient creature, Has already become extinct in the outside world.
According to the ancient scriptures,
The Heavenly Dragon has the blood of a dragon.
If it can pass many lightning tests,
perhaps,
it can evolve to be on par with the Ancient Dragon.
In front of the Ancient Dragon,
he is just a small worm.
How about we compensate him?
He looks pitiful.
Sorry.
If it wasn't for necessity,
I wouldn't want to rob you of your treasure.
You have dragon blood,
it's hard to transform.
This is the ripe grass of change,
to help you transform.
As compensation.
How?
Teacher.
You can soon return to peak strength.
This ancient forest,
The sound of monsters keeps coming.
It seems like a lot of strong people are coming.
Boss, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Zi Yan.
Nearby,
It seems like something is calling me.