♪Meteor cuts through the silence of the night♪
♪Moonlight ignites remembrance and sighs♪
♪How much brilliance is yet unfinished♪
♪How long the road ahead is yet unexplored?♪
♪How can I bear to be separated from you?♪
♪Are you calling me with tears?♪
♪Otherwise, how could I feel the
rain flowing around my ears?♪
♪Even my life is not resigned to my pity.♪
♪So my eyes flicker again♪
♪Fortunately, I still have you by my side♪
♪Fortunately, you still believe in my return♪
♪Even time changes unpredictably♪
♪You're still willing to accompany
me for much more longer♪
♪Fortunately, the abyss can find warmth♪
♪Fortunately, you also miss me♪
♪Time goes by, you and I♪
♪The story is to be continued♪
♪Meteor cuts through the silence of the night♪
♪Moonlight ignites remembrance and sighs♪
♪How much brilliance is yet unfinished?♪
♪How long the road ahead is yet unexplored?♪
♪How can I bear to be separated from you?♪
♪Fortunately, I still have you by my side♪
♪Fortunately, you still believe in my return♪
♪Even time changes unpredictably♪
♪You're still willing to accompany
me for much more longer♪
♪Fortunately, you still understand my glance back♪
♪Fortunately, you also miss me♪
♪Time flows, your company♪
♪Firm and determined♪
♪I heard you're calling me♪
♪My heart crazily fluttered in a sudden♪
♪I'm not resigned to the impossibility of my return♪
♪And the fade of our memories♪
♪I still want to fight with you for the coming days♪
♪And wait for the dust to settle♪
♪Never end, never lost♪
♪You and I are continuing♪
♪Fortunately, I still have you by my side♪
♪Fortunately, you still believe in my rebirth♪
♪Even time changes unpredictably♪
♪You're still willing to accompany
me for much more longer♪
♪Fortunately, you still understand my glance back♪
♪Fortunately, you also miss me♪
♪Time goes by, we lock eyes♪
♪The story is to be continued♪
[Battle Through the Heavens]
[Turmoil in the Central Plains]